<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>

<videos>
  <video name="Distracted Mind">
  	<caption>(9:32)
Final Cut Pro	 
Soundtrack Pro

Story revolves around friend who suffers from ADD but whose life is transformed once he 'over-doses' on his medication. Written, directed, shot, and edited by me and small crew of students. 

Parody of 'Requiem for a Dream' (2000), however, instead of narcotics destroying lives, here we have prescribed medications improving them.</caption>
 	 <path>images/video/add.flv</path>
  </video>
   <video name="Stop Motion Animation">
	<caption>[2:33]/Final Cut Pro/Stop Motion Editor

Silent stop motion short video I made exlporing stop motion technologies and programs.

The symbolism here regards boxes and containers and how we tend to catogorize and place others in our own predisposed conventions of how they should act and present themselves.</caption>
 	 <path>images/video/animation.flv</path>
  </video>
  <video name="Beltran Credits">
    <caption>(33;19)
AutoDesk Combustion 4
Adobe After Effects
Final Cut Pro
Soundtrack Pro

Final project for typography class, 'Type in Motion'.

Here I really payed attention and meticulously tweaked the movement of the type, which resulted in a smooth, easy-on-the eye, and modern motion. I also mixed the audio specifically for this piece and was asked permission from numerous student for use of it in other projects.</caption>
 	 <path>images/video/credits.flv</path>
  </video>
  <video name="Gamed">
	 <caption>(4:01)
Final Cut Pro
Autodesk Combustion 4
Adobe After Effects
Soundtrack Pro

Student film for special effects class. Displays use of multiple layered masks and light particle manipulation. Some light rotoscoping was also involved.

Mixed audio specifically for this project with Soundtrack Pro.

</caption>
	  <path>images/video/gamed.flv</path>
  </video>
  <video name="Visual Music">
	 <caption>(2:03)
Final Cut Pro
Adobe After Effects
Soundtrack Pro

Visual Music Text.
</caption>
	  <path>images/video/visualmusic.flv</path>
  </video>
  <video name="Man With a Digital Camera">
    <caption>(6:10)
Final Cut Pro

Final project for 'micro-cinema' project. Video was made to be viewed on hand held digital video device. 

Piece was inspired by Dziga Vertov's "Man with a Movie Camera" (1929), but instead of a day in Moscow portrayed on film, we expereience a day at the University of Oregon portrayed with digital video.

Piece was selected for viewing at the LaVerne Crosse gallery on campus after it was selected for the University's competitive summer film festival for creativity.</caption>
	  <path>images/video/micro.flv</path>
  </video>
  <video name="Technical Difficulties">
    <caption>(8;58)
Final Cut Pro
Compressor

Final project for digital video class. Focus was on use of cinemetography as medium of telling story and use of color to portray mood. 

Narrative follows Eric on how a day of technical difficulties leads to him losing his job. Critique on technology and how we depend on it too much at times.</caption>
 	 <path>images/video/techdif.flv</path>
  </video>
   <video name="Elders Interviews">
    <caption>[6;56]Final Cut Pro
	Elder Interview text goes here.</caption>
 	 <path>images/video/elders_presentation.flv</path>
  </video>
</videos>